cryptoblox.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy / Disclaimer | CryptoBlox

## _Privacy Policy_

(This privacy policy is applicable to the CryptoBlox.com web site) 

We take your privacy seriously. This policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. 

### Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets us know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content. 

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

### Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. 

### Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end users browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). 

## _Disclaimer_

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by CryptoBlox.com and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk. 

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website. 

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, CryptoBlox.com takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control. 

Use of any and all 3rd Party links and advertisments will be used at your own risk and discresion. By clicking on any links or advertisements you agree to comply with any laws relating to yourself including but not limited to gambling or any other activites. CryptoBlox.com will not be resonsible for any activity outide of our site by means of provided adverstisements and links. 

We do not endorse the product, service, or company, nor any of the claims made by links and/or banner ads in this website. Please do your own due dilligence before purchasing any of the products or services advertised here. 

Any exchange rates displayed are provided by 3rd party services. 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site Privacy Policy and Disclaimer. 

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
